<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manuel Pasieka</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/</link><description>Recent content on Manuel Pasieka</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austrian Ai Podcast</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/aaip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/aaip/</guid><description>The Austrian Ai Podcast is a window to projects and companies in the area of Artificial Intelligence in Austria.
Through guest interviews from experts in industry, research and the public sector I explore what the Austrian AI landscape has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/services/</guid><description>Training &amp;amp; Workshops Machine Learning (ML) has moved from a mere buzzword to a key ingredient of any forward-looking company. Although it&amp;rsquo;s clear that ML is the future, it is still a challenge to know how to leverage ML for your particular business. What do the advances in ML mean for your market? How can you make use of them in your products and services?
I will give workshops for you that will bring you up to speed with what really works in ML and how you can make the most of it for business.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/about-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/about-me/</guid><description>Manuel Pasieka Since 2022 I am helping companies in the DACH region to leverage the power of machine learning for their business.
Prior I have been working for 15 years as an Engineer in a variety of companies ranging from Startups, Research Institutes to SMB&amp;rsquo;s. Solving challenging tasks in teams or by myself.
I have one master&amp;rsquo;s degree in &amp;ldquo;parallel and distributed computing&amp;rdquo; and another one in &amp;ldquo;Artificial Intelligence&amp;rdquo; and worked as a Senior Data Scientist and Machine Learning Engineer.</description></item><item><title>Legal notice</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/legalnotice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/legalnotice/</guid><description>Manuel Pasieka
Jedleseer Strasse 75 1210 Vienna Austria
Tel: +43 681 81613940 E-mail: hello@manuelpasieka.com
VAT ID: ATU 77519829 Commercial Register:
Jurisdiction: Vienna, Austria Chamber of Commerce membership: Handelskammer Wien</description></item><item><title>privacy policy</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/privacypolicy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/privacypolicy/</guid><description>General information on data protection in Austria Data protection is a fundamental right enshrined in the Charter of Fundamental Rights of the European Union and in ยง 1 of the DSG (Austrian Data Protection Act). From 25 May 2018 on, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is in force in the European Union. At the same time, the new Austrian Data Protection Act (Datenschutzgesetz, DSG) enters into force in Austria.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/projects/first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:41:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/projects/first-post/</guid><description>This is my first post!
Some heading This supports markdown, right?
![tn.png]</description></item></channel></rss>