<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Manuel Pasieka</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/</link><description>Recent content on Manuel Pasieka</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Austrian Ai Podcast</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/aaip/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/aaip/</guid><description>The Austrian Ai Podcast is a window to projects and companies in the area of Artificial Intelligence in Austria.
Through guest interviews from experts in industry, research and the public sector I explore what the Austrian AI landscape has to offer.</description></item><item><title>Services</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/services/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2021 17:46:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/services/</guid><description>Training &amp;amp; Workshops Machine Learning (ML) is a powerful technology that can help you accelerate your business with new services and products if you know how to apply it correctly.
I can provide you with training and workshops ranging from the business perspective to specific technologies in machine learning.
Feasibility Study The applications of ML to improve business are huge, but how do you apply them to your company and your specific product?</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/about-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/about-me/</guid><description>Manuel Pasieka I am a Senior Machine Learning Engineer for hire and can help you to apply the transformative power of machine learning and artificial intelligence in your products and services.
My background is in computer science, with one master&amp;rsquo;s degree in distributed systems and another in machine learning. I have worked in small startups, consultancy companies, within and next to research labs, and product development companies. More details you can find on my linkedin profile.</description></item><item><title>Datenschutzerklärung</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/datenschutz/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/datenschutz/</guid><description>Inhaltsverzeichnis Einleitung und Überblick Anwendungsbereich Rechtsgrundlagen Kontaktdaten des Verantwortlichen Speicherdauer Rechte laut Datenschutz-Grundverordnung Sicherheit der Datenverarbeitung Kommunikation Webhosting YouTube Datenschutzerklärung Einleitung und Überblick Wir haben diese Datenschutzerklärung (Fassung 12.11.2021-111876675) verfasst, um Ihnen gemäß der Vorgaben der Datenschutz-Grundverordnung (EU) 2016/679 und anwendbaren nationalen Gesetzen zu erklären, welche personenbezogenen Daten (kurz Daten) wir als Verantwortliche &amp;#8211; und die von uns beauftragten Auftragsverarbeiter (z.</description></item><item><title>Impressum</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/impressum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/impressum/</guid><description>Informationspflicht laut §5 E-Commerce Gesetz, §14 Unternehmensgesetzbuch, §63 Gewerbeordnung und Offenlegungspflicht laut §25 Mediengesetz.
Manuel Pasieka
Manuel Pasieka
Musterstrasse 1, Stiege 1 Tür 1, 1234 Musterhausen, Österreich
Unternehmensgegenstand: IT Dienstleistungen
UID-Nummer: ATU12345678
GLN: 1234567891234
GISA: 12345678
Firmenbuchnummer: 123456a
Firmenbuchgericht: Musterhausen
Firmensitz: 1234 Musterhausen
Tel.: 01234/56789
Fax: 01234/56789-0
E-Mail: office@musterfirma.com Mitglied bei: WKO, Landesinnung, etc.
Berufsrecht: Gewerbeordnung: www.ris.bka.gv.at
Aufsichtsbehörde/Gewerbebehörde: Bezirkshauptmannschaft Musterhausen
Berufsbezeichnung: Webdesigner, Grafiker
Verleihungsstaat: Österreich
Kontaktdaten des Verantwortlichen für Datenschutz Sollten Sie Fragen zum Datenschutz haben, finden Sie nachfolgend die Kontaktdaten der verantwortlichen Person bzw.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/projects/first-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 22:41:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.manuelpasieka.com/en/projects/first-post/</guid><description>This is my first post!
Some heading This supports markdown, right?
![tn.png]</description></item></channel></rss>